My name is Oliver Queen.
我叫Oliver Queen
After five years on a hellish island,
经过岛上的五年炼狱生活
I have come home with only one goal-- to save my city.
我回家只有一个目的 拯救我的城市
But to do so,I can't be the killer I once was.
我不能再像以前一样成为杀手
To honor my friend's memory, I must be someone else.
为祭奠我的朋友 我必须扮成某人
I must be something else.
我必须掩盖身份
Previously on "Arrow"... As much as I would love to make this city safer,
绿箭侠 前情提要 尽管我很想让这个城市变得更安全
my first obligation is to Queen Consolidated and yours is,too.
我的首要职责 是保住Queen集团 你也是
I did some reading up on Lawton.
我仔细调查了Lawton
Lyla,listen-- Did you really think I wouldn't find out that he killed your brother?
- Lyla 听着 - 你以为我不知道是他杀了你弟弟吗
That you were using me?
你在利用我
I need to see this guy in a bag.
他必须死
You,of all people,should get that.
你应该比其他任何人都懂
Long time particularly for Bratva captain.Mr.Queen.
好久不见 尤其是黑手党首领 Queen先生
Anatoly Knyazev, he speaks very highly of you.He should.
- Anatoly Knyazev 他对你评价很高 - 必须的
I saved his life.
我救过他
You were supposed to sign this report at last night's board meeting.
你应该在上次董事会上 就签了这份报告的
You know why you didn't?
知道为什么没签吗
Probably because I didn't attend last night's board meeting.
也许是因为上次会议我没参加
Where were you?
那你在哪
I have other interests outside of this company.
除了这个公司之外我还有别的业务
I don't.
我没有
Mr.Queen-- I thought you were serious when you said we were partners.
Queen先生 你说我们是合伙人 我以为你是认真的
Isabel,I missed one meeting.
Isabel 我只不过没参加一次会议
This week.Last week,it was two meetings.
那是这周 上周还有两次
Mr.Queen.
Queen先生
Companywide revenue is at double digits since you and I took over.
自从我们接管后 公司收入急速增长
- Oliver! - Yes?
- Oliver - 什么事
I'm sorry to interrupt your... Grr!
抱歉打扰你们了
Um,I need to talk to you about your plans for this evening.
我需要跟你说下今晚的安排
With Mr.Harper?
和Harper先生的
You'll have to excuse me.
我得走了
We have work to do.It's important.
我们还有活要干 这很重要
So are my evening plans.
我今晚的安排也很重要
I'm sorry.
失陪
We are going to have to work on your excuses.
我们得给你想点高明的借口
You're right.
没错
You should be more careful.
你应该多加防备
You're completely exposed.
你现在完全暴露在外
I knew you were there.
我知道你在
What,you wanted me to tell you when the funny money guys were ready to make a sale?
你要我告诉你 贩卖假钞的人什么时候行动
Here we go.
我们现在可以开始了
Not "we." Go home.
没有我们 你回家
I already have help.
我有帮手
Here's the fake.
这是假货
Let's see the real.
再看看真货
You got two right above you.
你右上方有两个
Another at your six.
六点钟方向还有一个
Stay where you are,don't move!
住手 别动
I want to make a citizen's arrest.
我在执行公民逮捕
Don't move.
别动
That's it.I'm clear.
完事了 我撤了
Task force X to Mockingbird.
X特遣队呼叫知更鸟
We have the prize,we're coming home.
目标到手 我们回来了
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-可可与可心 pluto无肉筋
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 看糖 禾希饭 DB CXRR 金万藏 佐佐木 Crystal 校对: Andrea∞Quinn 时间轴:YTET-可可与可心 pluto无肉筋
Arrow Season 2 Episode 06
绿箭侠 第二季 第六集
Who are you people?
你们是谁
NSA?CIA?
国家安全局 情报局
My name is Amanda Waller.
我是Amanda Waller
I thought you A.R.G.U.S.guys were supposed to be more subtle.
我以为你们做事会精细点
For us,this was subtle.
对我们来说算精细了
Then I want to see Lyla Michaels.
我要见Lyla Michaels
So do I.
我也想
Agent Michaels has gone dark.
Michaels特工已经不知去向
Lyla's missing?
Lyla失踪了吗
What happened?
怎么回事
She was running down a lead in Moscow.
她去莫斯科查一个线索
She's missed two of her scheduled call-ins.
她已经缺席了两次日常电话报告
Well,what are you doing about it?
那你们打算怎么办
Speaking to you.
找你谈话
Even if we knew where in Russia Lyla is,
即使我们知道Lyla具体在俄罗斯哪
my superiors believe sending in an extraction team
我的上级也会认为再派出一支部队
could cause an international incident.
会引起国际纠纷
As far as they're concerned, she's already a framed picture on our lobby wall.
对他们来说 Lyla已经死了
Why are you telling me all this?
为什么告诉我这些
Because I know how you and Oliver Queen spend your nights.
因为我知道你和Oliver Queen 每天晚上在忙些什么
And I know your passport is up to date.
我也知道你的护照还没过期
It would help to start with what Lyla was doing in Moscow in the first place.
那你告诉我Lyla去莫斯科干什么
What was this lead she was tracking down?
她要找什么线索
A line on the whereabouts of Floyd Lawton.
Floyd Lawton的下落
Deadshot.
死亡射手
Lyla was in Russia for me,
Lyla去俄罗斯是为了我
Agent Michaels is an asset I can't easily replace.
Michaels特工对我有不可取代的价值
I know you find her similarly irreplaceable.
我知道你也认为她是不可取代的
Bring her home,Mr.Diggle.
把她带回来 Diggle
Thanks.
谢谢
It's been a while since I arrested you.
好久没逮捕你了
I'd forgotten how good it feels.
我都忘了那感觉多好了
I was working for...him.
我在为他做事
Him who?
哪个他
The guy who cost you your shield.
你在掩护的那个人
I'm on his team.
我和他是一伙的
You are,too.
你也是
Anybody else having serious deja vu?
似曾相识的感觉啊
That's all right,we're letting him go.
没关系 我们正要放了他
Our mistake.
我们搞错了
He was just in the wrong place at the wrong time.
他只是在错误的时间 出现在了错误的地点
Ok,uh,let's just get out of here before anyone changes their mind.
好吧 趁有人改变主意前 我们抓紧离开这里吧
The potentially catastrophic risk of turning on this machine
打开这台机器可能导致的灾难性后果
far outweigh any scientific gain that might come from it.
远大于其可能带来的科学收获
The people need to understand just how dangerous technology like this is.
人们必须明白像这样的技术有多危险
And the very real possibility of a cataclysmic event.
以及其可能导致的灾难性事件
Where'd you go?
你去哪儿了
Is everything ok?
没出什么事吧
Yeah.
没事
Just need a few personal days.
只是要请几天假处理一些私事
What's going on?
发生什么了
Have to help a friend.
得去帮朋友一个忙
Who?
哪个朋友
Lyla Michaels.
Lyla Michaels
It's his spy girlfriend that works for A.R.G.U.S.
他的特工女友 为超能力研究组工作
She went to Russia looking for Deadshot, for me.
她去了俄国找死亡射手 为了我
Now she's missing.
现在她失踪了
Felicity... I think it's time we visited our Queen Consolidated subsidiary in Moscow.
Felicity 我想是时候去莫斯科 看看Queen集团的子公司了
Yeah.
没错
Oliver,what are you doing?
Oliver 你这是在干什么
Just need to help a friend.
只是帮朋友一个忙
I can't ask you to do that.
我不能要求你这么做
You didn't.
你没有要求我
Sara... My name's Ivo.
- Sara - 我叫Ivo
What's your name?
你叫什么名字
Tommy.
Tommy
So.
那么
How did you come to be on this island,Tommy?
你是如何到这座岛上的呢 Tommy
I assume it wasn't by choice.
我想不会是你自愿来的吧
My,uh... Boat was shipwrecked here.
我的船遇到了海难
And I was the only survivor.
我是唯一的幸存者
Well,I'm sorry to hear that.
很遗憾听到这个消息
Did you explore the island much?
那你有没有探索过这座岛屿呢
Some of it.
一部分吧
Why?
为什么这么问
You didn't happen to run across a Japanese Imperial Navy submarine,did you?
你不会刚好发现了一艘 日本皇家海军的潜艇吧 有没有
During World War II, every country was trying to develop the ultimate weapon.
二战时 每个国家都在研究终极武器
The United States had the Manhattan Project,of course;
美国有曼哈顿计划 不必多说
the Nazis had das Uranverein.
德国搞了"铀俱乐部"
And the Japanese,well, they had Mirakuru.
至于日本人 他们开发了Mirakuru
Stem cell and genetic therapies, decades ahead of their time.
干细胞和基因疗法 领先时代数十年
Every war advances the cause of science.
每次战争 都会促进科学进步
And the Japanese,they had developed a serum that caused increased strength.
日本人发明了一种血清 可以增加力量
Rapid cell regeneration.
促进细胞再生
They called it Mirakuru.
他们称之为Mirakuru
"Miracle.
"奇迹"
" Thought they could create an army of super soldiers.
他们以为能创造出一支 由超级战士组成的军团
They were transporting their only supply via submarine
他们用一艘潜艇运输唯一一批血清
when that sub came under heavy fire by the allied forces.
结果这艘潜艇遭到了盟军强大火力
And it ran aground in this chain of islands.
在这片群岛触礁搁浅
Thanks to you... We now know it's this island.
多亏了你 我们现在能确定就是在这座岛屿
You killed my friends.
是你杀了我的朋友们
Which means it's up to you... To help us find that sub.
也就是说只能靠你... 来帮我们找到那艘潜艇
Are you forgetting something?
你是不是忘了点什么
Where do you think you're going?
你们这是要去哪里
Tahiti.
塔希提岛
That's funny.
有意思
The flight manifest says you're going to Moscow.
飞行记录显示你们要去莫斯科
Well,we're going to stop by there, you know,after Tahiti.
我们会顺路在那儿停一下 你懂的 在去塔希提岛后
What kind of partner decides to interact with our overseas holdings behind the other one's back?
什么样的合伙人会背着其他人去 我们的海外公司访问呢
It was an oversight.
是我疏忽了
Well,lucky for our partnership, I'm a fast packer.
幸运的是 我这个合伙人收拾行李很快
Oliver,her tagging along does not help matters any.
Oliver 她一路跟着可没什么好处
I will take care of her.
我会看好她的
John.
John
We're going to bring Lyla back.
我们会把Lyla带回来的
Wherever she is.
不论她在哪儿
I've arranged a meeting with the chief operating officer
明天上午十点我安排了一个
of our Moscow subsidiary tomorrow at 10:00 a.m.
与莫斯科子公司运营总裁的会议
Try your hardest not to miss this one.
可别又错过了
You know,I'm not this person that you seem to think I am.
我不是你想的那种人
- That depends. - On what?
- 那得看情况 - 什么情况
On if I think you use the corporate jet for a weekend of fun with your assistant.
比如当我发现你用集团的飞机跟 你的助手出去欢度周末的时候
Excuse me?
你在说什么
A blonde I.T.girl all of a sudden
一个金发IT美女
gets promoted to be assistant to the C.E.O.?
突然被提拔成CEO的助理
There are only two ways that happens.
只有两种可能
One is nepotism, and she doesn't look like your cousin.
一种情况是她是你的亲戚 但她明显不是
That...is... absolutely not happening.
真的不是你想的那样
What were her qualifications?
那她到底有什么资历
Aside from an abundance of short skirts.
除了她那一条又一条的超短裙
Her skirts aren't that...short.
她的裙子也没那么 短
What was that about?
你们说什么呢
Nothing.
没什么
Everything with Knyazev is set.
Knyazev那边已经安排好了
You have friends in the Russian mafia?
你还有俄罗斯黑手党的朋友
Color me at not at all surprised.
就当我一点都不惊讶好了
You're going straight to the hotel in a cab.
你直接打车去酒店吧
No,you're leaving me with her?
不 你要抛下我一个人 跟她一起走吗
Dig and I need to get a drink.
Dig和我得去喝一杯
Well...I...wouldn't mind a drink.
我不介意也喝一点儿啊
Ms.Loring.
Loring女士
Didn't take you for the club-hopping type.
没想到你是会来夜店的人
Well,I'm here on business.
我来办正事
Is everything ok with my mom?
我妈妈没事吧
We need to discuss something about this case.
正好 我们得谈谈这事
Your boyfriend Roy was arrested last night.
你男朋友昨晚被警方拘捕了
I know,but it was actually a misunderstanding.
我知道 这事有点误会
He got released.
他已经被释放了
Well,a few reporters got hold of the story
但是有些狗仔抓住你母亲不放
and they now know you're dating a known felon.
现在 你跟小混混交往的事 已经变成了他们的口舌
Thea,your mother is on trial for her life.
Thea 你母亲的案子生死攸关
Her whole defense pivots on being seen as a loving mother
她所有的辩护都建立在
who did what she had to do to protect her children,
全心全意为你们俩考虑的基础上
what kind of parent she was.
因为她是一位伟大的母亲
We need the people to know that she raised you to make good decisions.
我们希望其他人看到的是两个 家教良好 正直的孩子
So if you care about your mom, you're going to have to end this relationship immediately.
如果你还顾念你的母亲 就该立刻和对方分手
Oliver Queen?
Oliver Queen
My favorite American!
我最喜欢的美国人
Dabro pazhalavat.
Dabro pazhalavat
It has been too long.
好久不见
John Diggle,this is Anatoly Knyazev.
John Diggle 这位是Anatoly Knyazev
Thank you for meeting us.
感谢你抽空见我们
If Oliver vouches for you, you're my second favorite American.
你有了Oliver作担保 就是仅次于Oliver的我最喜欢的美国人
First,a toast.
先来干一杯
None for me,thanks.
我不喝酒 谢谢
Prochnost.
干杯
To strength.
强者更强
Now.Business.
现在可以谈正事了
This is woman you look for,yes?
这个女的就是你要找的人吧
Picture is from two days ago,from gulag-- prison.
这相片是两天前在古拉格监狱拍下的
Lyla was arrested?
Lyla被抓了
Not quite.
不尽然
From what I hear,she was trying to break in.
据我所知 她是试图闯进监狱
Why?
为什么
I do not know.
我不知道
But clearly she had issues breaking back out.
可惜她出不来了
Gulag,worst in Russia.
古拉格 俄国最恐怖的监狱
It's called Koshmar.
被称为Koshmar
The nightmare.
噩梦
It's full of violent psychopaths and killers.
里面有各种各样心理变态的暴力分子 还有杀人犯
And that's just the guards.
这些还都只是看守
Anatoly,we need a way into the gulag to extract her.
Anatoly 我们得进去把她救出来
You get in,you get shot before you get out.
还没等你出来 就挨枪子了
Or end up like your friend.
或者干脆出不来了
Mmm,it's impossible.
你救不了她
The only thing that's impossible is us leaving this country without this woman.
不把她救出来 我绝不会离开俄罗斯
I like this guy.
挺对我胃口
We have no word for "optimist" in Russian.
在俄罗斯 没有"乐观"这个词
The only way in to Koshmar is as prisoner.
想进古拉格 唯一的办法就是成为那里的犯人
Now,I have guard there,owes me favor.
里面有个看守欠我个人情
It could work.
我们可以找他
I'll give you one shot in twenty.
但是你只有5%的可能会成功
- Set it up.I'll go. - No.
- 你安排吧 我进去 - 不
- It has to be me.
- 让我去
Oliver,what if something happens to you in there?
Oliver 你不能有事
What happens to me,Felicity,or Isabel,for that matter?
如果是我 Felicity 或者Isabel出事
You have to be on the outside making the moves.
你还可以在外面接应我们
I'll go inside.I've got this.
让我去 我没问题的
Now that is a lot of drugs.
带的有点多啊
Courtesy of Knyazev.
是Knyazev友情赞助的
About enough weight to land me in the Koshmar.
足够让我蹲古拉格了
You need to be wearing this when they process you.
你得穿上这个
Guards will take it,but that's the point.
好让看守把它没收
This... Is Knyazev's man inside the prison.
这位 就是Knyazev在监狱里的朋友
A guard.
那个看守
He'll know where in the gulag Lyla is being held.
他知道Lyla关在哪里
When all hell breaks loose, you need to meet us at the rendezvous point with Lyla,or...
得手之后 你和Lyla 得去约定的地方找我们 否则...
Or I am a permanent Russian.
我就得永远留在俄国了
Just thinking out loud... But,are we sure this is the best plan we can come up with?
我多嘴一句... 这就是我们的最佳方案了
I know Lyla's your friend,but... Felicity,Lyla isn't my friend.
- 我知道Lyla是你的朋友 但是... - Felicity Lyla不是我的朋友
She was my wife.
她是我的前妻
Explain that sentence.
能解释一下吗
Lyla and I met in the army back in Afghanistan.
Lyla和我在阿富汗军中相识
But we didn't stay married long once we got stateside.
但是回国后 我们的婚姻并没能维系下去
Couldn't figure out a way to stay married without a war to fight.
想来是因为没仗可打了 也就不会过日子了
So she joined A.R.G.U.S.
后来她加入了警卫队
and I circled back for my third tour.
而我第三次踏上了征途
I can't leave here without her,Felicity.
我一定要带她回去 Felicity
Just can't.
一定
Two minute warning.
还有两分钟
Good luck,John.
祝你好运 John
They have him.
他进去了
Clock's running.
行动开始
Zhivey,zhivey.
Zhivey zhivey
Hurry up.
快点
Khoroshaya kurtka.
外套不错
What,uh,crime fits your punishment?
你犯了什么事
Drugs.And you?
毒品 你呢?
I gave speech.
我发表了公开演说
About government corruption.
揭露政府的腐败行为
Right.
不意外
It is rare to see one of your people in Koshmar.
我们这像你这样的人可不多
What,American?
什么人 美国人
Chernokozhiy.
黑人
Ehh... Chernokozhiy not popular here.
黑人在这不太受欢迎
Shocker.
好怕怕呀
You think Dig's ok?
Dig不会有事的吧
I think he's doing the same as he was when you asked me five minutes ago.
我想他跟五分钟前你问我时一样没问题
They're coming.
他们来了
They sell us Russian police truck for cheap.
就是他们把俄国警车便宜卖给我们
Vot mashina,kotoraya vam nuzhna.
这是你要的东西
Sto pyatisot tysyach rubley.
这是一百五十万
Na koleni.
跪下
Yesli vy sde syete eto, moi lyudi vas, I vashi deti osanutsya sirotami.
不给我就杀了你全家
What'd you say?
你跟他说了什么
Please.
求他
You know,in Russia,there is gulag.
知道吗 在俄国有个集中营
Almost as bad as this.
几乎跟这儿一样糟
Sara-- Don't say my name.
- Sara - 别叫名字
If they find out we know each other,they'll kill us both.
被他们发现我们认识 我们都会被杀的
I thought you drowned.
我以为你淹死了
When I came up,the boat was gone.
当我醒来时 船已经不见了
And I thought you were,too.
我以为你也淹死了
And I was floating out there for days when this ship... They found me.
我在海上漂了几天后 这艘船...他们发现了我
And they saved me.
然后救了我
Is that why you're helping them?
所以你帮他们做事
I don't have a choice.
我别无选择
I need to warn my friends.
我得去警告我的朋友们
You said they were dead.
你不是说他们死了
They're not that easy to kill.
他们可没那么容易就死了
Try not to move.
别乱动
It smells like puke!
这东西闻着真恶心
It'll heal your wounds.
这对伤口有好处
You have to go.
你必须走
Get out of here.
离开这儿
Get to higher ground.
去高点的地方
I'm not leaving you.
我不会离开你的
I will not be the reason something happens to you.
我不能拖累你
Then we're in agreement.
那就没什么问题了
Because I make my own choices.
这是我自己的选择
You are a strong woman.
你是个坚强的女人
When I care about someone,there's nothing I won't do for them.
我会为我关心的人做任何事
Another thing... we have in common.
我们又有个...共同点了
The burns,they're lowering your body temperature.
烧伤降低了你的体温
Here.
过来
Where you been all night?
你整晚都去哪儿了
Working.
干活
Well,you deserve a break.
你该好好歇歇
Um,actually,I've been thinking.
其实 我想了想
Maybe we should take some space.
或许我们该给彼此多点空间
I mean,we work together and live together.
我是说我们朝夕相处
It's kind of getting hard to breathe.
都快窒息了
Since when?
什么时候开始这么觉得的
Oh,wait,does this have to with that lawyer lady dropping by?
等等 这跟那个蹦出来的女律师有关系吗
No,this has to do with the fact
不 这跟你上个月
that you've been arrested twice in the last month.
被逮捕的就有两次有关
Come on. I've been trying to stay out of trouble.
别这样 我已经尽量避免惹麻烦了
My body hasn't had a scratch on it in weeks.
这几周我连个擦伤都没有
Well,I mean,excluding the ones that you put there.
我是说除了你抓的那几道
And the other night?
那天晚上呢
Was a misunderstanding.
那是个误会
Roy... This just isn't working,ok?
Roy...我做不来
Not for me.
实在办不到
Thea,you can't mean that.
Thea 你不是那个意思对吗
I do. I'm sorry.
我就是那个意思 对不起
Those men... They are Vory.
那些人... 他们很好斗
They are in charge.
而且很有势力
It's best to stay away.
最好离他们远点
American... You are suka now.
美国佬... 现在起你是我的玩物
Are we seriously going to do this?
真的要这么做吗
Guess so.
我想是的
Fighting strictly prohibited.
严禁打架
Vodki,pozhaluysta.
请给我杯伏特加
You missed the tour.
你错过演出了
What happened to you?
发生了什么事
I saw a Russian vehicle that I simply had to have.
我看到了一辆我以前有过的俄国车
Is that why you came to Russia?
这是你来俄国的目的吗
Car shopping?
买车
Oh,I just ordered one.
我只点了一杯
One's for me.
这杯是我的 再来一杯
This cold room.
这是个冷藏室
Six hours for you.
你要在这儿待6个小时
Six hours? You can't keep me in here that long.
6个小时 你不能关我这么久
Now seven hours.
那就7小时
Well,that was pretty stupid... Then again,
你那么做太傻了...而且
you never really were one of the brightest guys.
你确实也不是什么聪明人
Deadshot.
死亡射手
Your spine frozen through yet?
你脊柱冻透了没
Trust me.
相信我
My problem here isn't with the cold.
这点冷才不是我现在的最大问题
What,you still haven't forgiven me for shooting your brother?
什么 你还没原谅我杀了你哥哥吗
Man,you really hold a grudge.
伙计 你还真记仇
I know why you're here.
我知道你来这儿干嘛
That girl.
那个女孩
From A.R.G.U.S.
来自警卫队的
Lyla didn't find a lead on you.
看来Lyla不止找到了关于你的线索
She found you.
而且找到了你
- Does everyone really think that Felicity and I are... - No.
- 大家真的认为我跟Felicity是... - 没有
Just everyone who works at Queen Consolidated.
只是在Queen集团工作的人都这么认为
She's just a friend.
我跟她只是朋友
You don't seem like the kind of man who has female friends.
你看着不像有女性朋友的人
Can I ask you a personal question?
我能问你个私人问题吗
With some vodka in me,I just might answer.
喝了几杯伏特加 我或许会回答吧
Why does saving my family's company mean so much to you?
为什么救我家族的公司对你那么重要
Despite what Sheryl Sandberg might say...
女强人Sheryl Sandberg不会那么说的...
It still isn't that easy to make it as a woman in business.
但女人在商场打拼还是不容易
I've...given up a lot.
我...放弃了很多东西
Which means if I don't succeed at everything, then what was the point?
如果我不能成功 那有何意义
May I ask you a personal question?
我能问你一个私人问题吗
Others have tried and failed.
其他人问过 但问了也白问
Why do you try so hard to make me think that you're a lazy idiot?
你为何这么想 让我认为你是个懒惰的白痴
I know you're not.
我知道你不是
Underneath that swagger,I see you pretty clearly.
在你的伪装下 我能清楚地看到
Really?
是吗
And what do you see?
你看到什么了
You're intelligent.
你很聪明
Driven.
有紧迫感
And lonely.
还很孤独
How do you see that?
你怎么看出来的
Because it's what I see when I look in the mirror.
因为我也是那样的人
We don't have much time.
我们时间不多了
- There you go. - Let's go,let's go.
- 走吧 - 走 走了
Nice seeing you,John.
很高兴见到你 John
Can ***
请问还需要点别的吗
I ***
我想不该再喝了
You speak Russian.
你会说俄语
ONLY ***
只跟我朋友说
I was raised in Moscow until I was nine.
直到九岁前 我都生长在莫斯科
And then adopted by a family that took me to America.
然后一个家庭把我收养到美国
Took me years to get rid of my accent.
我花了几年时间才改掉口音
It isn't easy making friends in grade school when you sound like Natasha.
俄国口音在小学交朋友可不容易
Sou ***
听起来你长久以来都很孤独
Pay ***
买单吧
I...Don't have a lot of time.
我...没有太多时间
I'll be quick.
我会很快的
Five minutes.Must hurry.
五分钟 必须快点
Remind me to get you a pack of cigarettes when this is all over.
等这事搞定了 记得提醒我给你买包烟
I don't smoke.
我不抽烟的
You weren't going to leave without me,were you?
你不会不带上我走吧
I should kill you right now!
我真该马上杀了你
You won't.
你不会的
Why?
为什么
BecauseI'm the only one who knows where your little girlfriend is.
因为只有我知道你女朋友关在哪里
You're not stupid.
你可不傻
You wouldn't put yourself in here without an exit strategy.
你没有逃离计划怎么会被关进来
I take you to the girl... You take me out.
我带你去找她...你带我出去
Isabel,I have to go.
Isabel 我得走了
Sorry.
抱歉
Do I strike you as someone who needs to cuddle?
我像是那种矫情的人吗
- Hi. - Hi. - It's time.Ready?
时候到了 准备好了吗
Yeah,I-- I think she can take the night off.
- 是的 我... - 我想她今晚可以休息了
Don't you?
是吗
Felicity... It--what happens in Russia stays in Russia.
- Felicity... - 发生在俄国的事过了就过了
Even when it makes no sense whatsoever.
尽管没什么意义
Guessin',uh,you want to hold on to that.
我看 枪还是你拿好了
This way.
这边
What were you thinking?
你在想什么啊
What?
什么
Over 64 million women over the age of consent in Russia and you sleep with her.
俄国有超过六千四百万 到了法定年龄的女人 你却跟她上床
So we're not doing the "What happens in Russia stays in Russia?
不是说"发生在俄国的事过去就过去了"吗
" We're still in Russia.
我们还在俄国
There is nothing money cannot buy in this country.
在这个国家没有钱是办不到的事
Diggle should be heading out Lyla in two minutes.
Diggle两分钟内会带Lyla出来
Well,breaking out of prison is harder than it looks.
越狱可不容易
You of all people should know that.
你们应该都知道吧
Stay quiet. Follow me.
别出声 跟我来
You'll remember the rest of us... Yes?
你会记得我们的吧...是吗
I promise.
我保证
I'll come back.
我会回来的
Come on.
快走
- Are we making a swim for it? - No.
- 我们要游过去吗 - 不
They'd shoot us the second we hit the water.
我们一下水他们就会开枪的
You said your friends,they have one of the radios from the ship,right?
你说你朋友 他们有一台船用收音机 对吗
Yeah.
是的
You look like you know what you're doing there.
看来你很会用嘛
In the past year,I've learned a lot of things I never expected to.
过去几年 我学了许多意想不到的东西
You and me both.
我们都是
They won't respond unless they hear your voice.
他们没听到你的声音是不会回应的
Shado.
Shado
ni neng ting dao wo ma
你能听到我吗
Slade.
Slade
Thank God you're alive.
谢天谢地 你还活着
Yeah,I'm on the freighter-- Sara,what are you doing?
- 是的 我在货船上... - Sara 你在干嘛
There's only two of them.
他们只有两个人
They haven't moved from the location of the mortar attack.
他们还没离开迫击炮的攻击范围
What the hell is going on here?
这到底是怎么回事
You just confirmed that your friends are alive.
你刚确认你的朋友还活着
Which means they're still a threat.
这意味着他们还是个威胁
You know,until we kill them.
在我们杀掉他们之前
You son of a bitch--oh!
你个狗娘养的
If I say she's in there, what's keeping you from shooting me?
如果我说她在里面 你要怎样才不会朝我开枪
Honor.
信誉
You should try it some time.
你也该试一试讲信誉
Lyla!
Lyla
Johnny?
Johnny
Ready to go home?
准备回家吧
You came for me.
你来救我了
I always have. Always will.
我一直会 以后也会
Deadshot's here.
死亡射手在这呢
- In the prison. - I know.
- 就在这监狱里 - 我知道
What's your extraction plan?
你打算怎么逃出去
Depends.
随机应变吧
What time is it?
现在几点
YOU ***
我穿着帅吧
Let's go,go,go,move,move,move!
走 我们走 快 快
This way.
这边
Got it. I shut down the phones.
搞定 我切断了通信
The guards can't call for help.
狱警们没法呼救了
Your friend and that woman are not here by now, they will not be here at all.
你朋友和那女的到现在还没出现 他们出不来了
Much better.
这下好多了
on***
都给我趴下
Oliver,get down!
Oliver 蹲下
Follow me!
跟我来
Move!
快
We're clear.
我们逃出来了
Stop the truck.
停车
Get out. Get out!
下车 快下车
Move.
快点
That's the thing about honor,John.
这是信誉问题 John
You can't turn it on and off.
你不会出尔反尔的
I'm just curious.
我只是好奇
How is it you think your brother ended up dead?
你知道你哥怎么死的吗
You shot a client that Andy was protecting, and you missed.
你要杀一个Andy保护的客户 结果你失手了
I don't miss.
我从未失手
Your brother was the contract.
你哥才是目标人物
Who would want to kill Andy?
谁想杀Andy
I don't know the names,just an alias.
不清楚 只知道一个化名
Hive.
Hive
Food for thought,John.
好好想吧 John
Food for thought.
够你想想的
Are we going to discuss what happened last night?
我们不聊聊昨晚的事吗
Why would we?
为什么呢
No reason.
不为什么
I'll see you in the office tomorrow.
明天公司见
Thank you.
多谢
You had my back.
你那么支持我
And now you know what it feels like.
所以现在你知道那是什么感觉了吧
Wh--what are you-- what are you doing here?
你在这干什么
Good question.
问得好
I've gotten a lot of calls from prison,
我接过很多从监狱打来的电话
but never from my girlfriend's mother.
但还没接到过我女友老妈打来的
It occurred to me
我突然想起来
that I've never been given the opportunity to meet the man in your life.
我一直没机会认识你生命中最重要的男人
I don't know if she told you, but your daughter kind of dumped me.
我不知道你女儿是否说过 她把我甩了
And what you should know is that she did it for me.
你要知道她是因为我才这样做的
Jean told me she came to see you.
Jean跟我讲她找过你
I told her she shouldn't have.
我告诉她不该那么做
Why didn't you just tell me the truth?
你为什么不跟我说实话呢
Us being together... It can hurt her case.
咱们在一起 会对妈的案子不利
Thea... Your social life is not going to be the determining factor in my trial.
Thea 你的社交生活 并不是影响我审判结果的决定因素
Sweetheart,what you've had to endure this last year
乖女儿 你去年所经历的事情
is more than most people go through in two lifetimes.
比多数人两辈子经历的还多
But you've not only survived,you've flourished.
但你不仅挺过来了 还有所成长
I think a lot of that has to do with Roy.
我想这跟Roy有很大关系
So,as your mother,I forbid you not to see him.
所以作为你的母亲 我不允许你们分手
Thank you.
谢谢
I have to admit, this is not how I anticipated my trip to Russia ending.
我不得不承认 这次俄国之行的结果不是我所预料的
I just feel lucky we made it out of there alive.
我只是庆幸我们能活着离开那里
Thank you.
谢谢你
Not just for coming for me.
不仅因为你来救我
For doing what you had to once you did.
还有你当时的选择
You mean working with Deadshot.
你是说跟死亡射手的合作么
You know,me and Carly broke up because I couldn't love her
你知道么 我跟Carly分手 是因为我不能在爱她的同时
and hate him at the same time.
又恨着他
I'm honored to be the exception.
很荣幸我是个例外
Lyla,you're always the exception.
Lyla 你永远是个例外
No,no,let Waller stew.
不 不 让Waller去做吧
Stay for breakfast.
你留下吃早餐
Throw in your blueberry pancakes
除非你做拿手的蓝莓饼
and you may be able to convince me.
我可能会考虑留下来
Can you deliver this to Isabel's office,please?
帮忙把这个送到Isabel的办公室
Why her?
为什么选择她
I mean,besides the... obvious leggy model reason.
我是说 除了她有长腿模特的身材
It just kind of happened.
顺其自然而已
It didn't mean anything.
并不代表什么
Because of the life that I lead...
因为我的生活
I just think that it's better to not...
我觉得最好还是不要...
Be with someone that I could really care about.
和我真正在乎的人在一起
Well,I think... I think you deserve better than her.
好吧 我觉得你值得比她更好的人
We have their location.
找到他们的位置了
This one's no longer of use to us.
他对我们而言不再有用了
Let's see how good you are... At removing a bullet from your head.
让我们看看你能有多大本事 可以取出你脑袋里的子弹
Wait!
等等
He could still be useful.
他或许还有用处
She's right.
她说得对
Once we get rid of his friends, we'll need him to lead us to the graves.
一旦我们干掉他那俩朋友 我们还需要他带我们去到那个墓穴
Sometimes I wonder who gives the orders here.
有时候我在想这里谁是老大
You... or your little bouzin.
是你... 还是你的小跟班
You're going back to the island.
你又要回岛上了
Oliver.
Oliver
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-------------------------- 本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用 禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负 --------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-pluto无肉筋 可可与可心
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 看糖 禾希饭 DB CXRR 金万藏 佐佐木 Crystal 校对: Andrea∞Quinn 时间轴:YTET-pluto无肉筋 可可与可心
Arrow Season 2 Episode 6
绿箭侠 第二季 第六集 完